<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Wikipedia</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="query_hint">Search Wikipedia</string>
    <string name="article1">Article 1</string>
    <string name="article2">Article 2</string>
    <string name="article3">Article 3</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="random">Random Article</string>
    <string name="random_article">The Statue of Liberty (Liberty Enlightening the World; French:
        La Liberté éclairant le monde) is a colossal neoclassical sculpture on Liberty Island
        in New York Harbor in New York City, in the United States. The copper statue, a gift from
        the people of France to the people of the United States, was designed by French sculptor
        Frédéric Auguste Bartholdi and built by Gustave Eiffel. The statue was dedicated on October
        28, 1886. (Full article...)</string>
    <string name="yesterday_article">Stephanus serrator is a species of parasitic wasp in the
        family Stephanidae, the crown wasps. This species is native to much of Europe and is to
        be seen in the breeding season on recently dead timber or wood products. The larvae are
        parasitoids of the larvae of wood-boring beetles. (Full article...) </string>
    <string name="today_article">The 2009 World Series was the championship series of Major League
        Baseball\'s 2009 season. Opening on October 28, it was a best-of-seven playoff between the
        Philadelphia Phillies, champions of the National League and defending World Series
        champions, and the New York Yankees, champions of the American League.
        The Yankees (Full article...)</string>
    <string name="log_in_title">Log in to your account</string>
    <string name="dont_have_account">Don\'t have an account? </string>
    <string name="join_wiki">Join Wikipedia.</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_pass">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="log_in_button">Log in</string>
    <string name="create_account_title">Create a new account</string>
    <string name="have_account">Already have an account? </string>
    <string name="log_in">Log in.</string>
    <string name="confirm_pass">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="create_account_button">Create your account</string>
    <string name="reset_pass_title">Reset password</string>
    <string name="fill_in">fill in one of the fields below to receive password reset
        instructions via email</string>
    <string name="or">Or</string>
    <string name="reset_button">Reset</string>
</resources>
